Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place?
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary?
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all!
Through all the trouble and times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain!
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on the crew.
We are
This looks suspiciously
like a treasure map,
and it seems to be pointing
to Cocoyashi Village.
I can't believe you have the nerve
to go through my personal belongings.
That's my map, and it has
nothing to do with you.
So angry.
Is there something on your mind?
What is this?
Why are all these guys
dead? What happened?
The pirate hunter Zoro did it.
Why weren't you here, Hachi? Huh?
This could have been
prevented had you been here.
Of course it could have,
had I only been here.
It's unforgivable.
We get it.
You weren't here, so you
don't know where he is.
Is that right?
Whoa.
Well, let me think about it.
I saw one guy.
Yeah, that's right.
He was a slightly
suspicious swordsman type.
Oh, that's him!
You did see him, you idiot!
So where did he go?
He told me he wanted to see Orlong, so
I gave him a ride to Cocoyashi Village.
Excellent.
That means we don't
have any need to hurry.
He's going to come straight to me.
Sorry, Orlong, but if I had known
you were going to be back so soon,
I would have kept him here for you.
But he said he was a guest and I thought I
should get him to the
village as fast as I could
Zoro, huh?
Which means if I could buy
just a little more time
Why do you keep getting in the way?
Everything's so close to working out
So close!
Ugggh! Egh!
Damn you, Nami!
You wanna fight, don't ya?
This is your fault, Dusak.
You're the one getting in the way.
This is what you get
for messing with Arlong!
Nami, you really disappointed me.
Even after you stole our ship and ran
off, Luffy had complete faith in you!
He trusts you completely, and you
haven't even shown an ounce of guilt!
How can you betray someone like that?
Are you really that cold-hearted?
The only thing I trust is money.
Those dumb enough to be fooled deserve it.
How can you say that?
You idiots.
It was going according to plan.
I'm not about to let you and your friends
ruin eight long years of hard work.
So long, Usopp.
It's just business.
You understand.
Well, I'll be damned.
Looks like you became a
pirate while you were gone.
So long.
What like you're gonna kill me?
That's right.
I wouldn't underestimate me.
Oh Crap if I stay here, I'm
a dead man special attack
Now's my chance.
This is just like something
you'd think of. Nami!
Don't do this.
It's for my business.
This was my only choice.
Nami, how could you?
Now go and die.
I can't believe it.
Big Tessnami killed Big Bro-O-Sup!
Your wish came true.
You died at sea.
Nami, I'm sorry for doubting you.
Without question, you're our friend.
Friend, huh?
There's only one reason
I joined this group.
And that's to buy
Cocoyashi Village from you.
You got that?
Just business, not friends.
Keep your end of the deal, and
I'll have those berries soon.
Yes, of course.
I'd rather cut my stomach open and die
than rake a promise concerning money.
That's the kind of man I am.
Glad to hear it, Arlong.
You know the score.
She gives me the creeps.
Oh, what a great woman she's become.
He's dead.
She killed him.
That witch killed him.
Oh, there it is!
Arlo Park!
Hey!
Keep up the pace, cow!
I feel sorry for it.
Sanji's kicks must have
really taken their toll.
Not that way!
Go to your other left!
To the building, stupid!
Oh, it's almost like we're flying!
Almost!
We are flying, you moron! No!
We're falling!
Man, they're successful!
Hey, girls!
Awesome! We're here, guys!
What the hell were you doing?
What do you mean?
We're here to pick up Nami. Duh.
How come you haven't found her yet?
Oh, yeah.
What about Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp? Oh, no. Come
on. We've got to hurry.
Why?
What's wrong?
That dumbass has been caught by Arlong.
We've got to hurry before they kill him.
He's already dead.
What?
We're too late.
Big bro Usopp is dead.
Tommy murdered him!
Come on, hurry up! What's the deal?
The marines are here, we're saved!
Some survivors from
Koza managed to contact
the government and they
told them what happened!
Now the marines are here to rescue us all!
See?
Finally, it's over!
Now we get to leave this horrible place!
So this is the infamous arlong park.
What is the world coming to when pirate
skunk can set up such an opulent base?
Listen up, men.
Our noble mission today
is one of extraction.
We must rescue the survivors
of the town of gosa,
which was savagely destroyed
by the arlong pirates.
But I am left to wonder would our
brand of swift and terrible justice
allow us to simply overlook the decadent
fortress of these unchecked brutes?
Sir? No. Sir. Correct.
Our unit must annihilate
arlong and his men.
Prepare for battle at once!
Yes, sir.
Is that right?
Marine branch 77?
That's right.
That's what I said.
A newcomer.
We'll have someone negotiate
with the man in charge.
If two million isn't enough to keep
them from trying anything funny,
then kill every last one of them.
Oh, no!
The marines have opened fire!
Orlog, watch out!
Whoa, he crushed a cannonball.
Those jaws are terrifying.
So what now?
Are the talks...
...canceled?
All right, let's do it!
It's gonna be a bloodbath!
Hold on, guys.
Not so fast.
There's no need to expend so much
energy just to take out the trash.
Just leave it to us.
What foolish humans they
are to pick a fight with us.
In our own waters, too.
Those marines don't stand a chance
against three of our leaders.
I doubt that ship will make
it a full three minutes.
That's odd.
Seems that cannonball was a dud.
Fire another!
This is a signal of open hostility!
Never drop your guard!
When you're dealing with fishmen.
Sir.
Mandel.
It's one of them.
Stand down! Right now!
One of our longsmen, yes.
I am Commodore Perona Perona.
Of Marines Branch No.
77 Allow me to elaborate You see, we are
a somewhat well-known elite marine unit.
Do you understand what
I'm telling you, fish man?
If you wish to live,
surrender immediately.
What have you done to him?
You killed him!
What's all this shaking?
Don't tell me there are
fish men under the ship.
I really am sorry to
inconvenience you like this,
but we just took the liberty
of removing your rudder.
Is that okay?
You what, Commodore?
Don't worry, I didn't hit
any of his vital organs.
Commodore, I have a question.
It's just hypothetical, of course.
If one were to move a large reef
directly into a strong current,
what do you suppose would
happen to the ocean?
What?
No, moving the whole reef?
That can't be done.
It's just not possible.
Put it down over there, Haji. Right.
Uh, Commodore, a giant
whirlpool's just appeared.
The rudder isn't working.
What?
I told you, we removed the rudder.
So now this rudderless ship is
headed straight to the sea floor.
You're dead!
That's right, and so is hope.
Time to face the truth.
There's no way to escape
Barlong's control.
I'll bet you're tired.
No, I didn't even break a sweat.
We know everything about these
waters, from the winds to the depths.
It was quite easy.
With our expert knowledge of
these waters, no one can beat us.
True, but let's not forget Nami's charts.
Indeed, they are excellent charts.
If we could persuade Nami to do
this for all the world's oceans,
we would be the undisputed
rulers of the sea forever.
I know, Nami's brilliant.
In fact, she could be critical in
the creation of the Arlong Empire.
It's just a shame. A shame?
He promised to let Nami
and Cocoyashi Village
go while she saves up a
hundred million berries.
Oh, no, seriously?
Whatever you do, you can't let her leave!
You can't!
I have to.
That's what we agreed
upon eight years ago.
I'm the kind of man who always keeps
my promises when it comes to money.
Always.
Say another word and you'll regret it!
Easy, Luffy.
This has nothing to do with Johnny.
Go on, believe whatever you want.
But I know what I saw!
Nami killed big bro Osop! Shut your mouth!
Never in a million years
would Nami kill Usopp!
She wouldn't do that to her friends!
But I saw it!
What was that about friends, Luffy?
Nami!
What are you doing here?
What are we doing here?
You're our friend!
We came to get you.
What a pest. Nami?
Friends, huh?
Don't make me laugh.
You're just pathetic enough
to deserve each other.
Damn you!
You killed him!
I watched you do it!
And now, Big Bro Osup is gone!
Yep, that's right.
So why don't you kill
me and get your revenge?
What?
Word to the wise fellas, because
of your friend's stupidity,
Arlong is preparing to kill
Zoro along with his entire crew.
And I don't care how monstrously
strong you guys think you are,
you're no match for the real monsters.
Hi, Nami!
It's me, Sanji!
Let's run away together!
Can it, Romeo?
This isn't the time or place for that!
Excuse me.
Love is like a hurricane, so back off!
Hey, look at me when I'm talking to you!
Nami, where is Usopp?
With the fishes. Damn it!
Cut the crap!
How sad.
A swordsman striking a lady.
Idiot!
Can't you see what's happening here?
You're starting to piss me off!
If someone had stopped me
that easily, I'd be mad, too.
What?
You should watch your mouth.
I'll say whatever I want, bastard.
Big bros!
We're all in this together, okay?
This is no time to fight!
Your pal's right.
Now quit your bickering and
leave while you still can.
You outsiders have no right to
butt into this island's affairs.
Don't you get it yet?
The only reason I got
close to you idiots was
so that I could rob you
of everything you had.
but now that you're broke, it
looks like the dream's dead.
So go, take your ship.
Go on, find a navigator dumb enough
to join you and go to the Grand Line.
Continue on your quest to find
the One Piece or whatever.
Just leave here, you're an eyesore.
Goodbye now.
Nami.
Big bro Luffy sleepy
sleep at a time like this
in the middle of the road
well i'm pretty tired.
I'm not gonna butt into
their affairs i'm not
interested but i'm not
leaving either night. Huh?
Fine.
Whatever!
Just go ahead and die! No!
Hey!
Big Bro Zoro!
What on earth are you thinking? Come on!
Did you forget that
Arlong is out to kill us?
We should be running away!
Now that we know what Nami's really like,
there isn't a single good reason
why we should stay on this island.
Right.
Understood.
Sorry to cut our reunion
short, but I won't stay.
My role as guide ends here.
Yeah, I'm with him.
I don't want to deliberately
get myself killed. Fine.
I'll see you around.
Until we meet again, big bro!
Take care, you guys! You too.
Hey, do you still honestly believe
that Nami could have killed Usopp?
When she did that...
It's for my business.
This was my only choice.
When she did that,
Nami stabbed her own hand to
make it look like she stabbed me.
I can't believe she did that for me.
But it's a good thing she did.
Otherwise, I'd be fish
food right now for sure.
But what do I do?
A manly man like me can't just turn
tail and run after being saved.
One step at a time.
Right now, I gotta hurry and find Zoro.
Is that him up ahead? It is! It's Zoro!
So Nami didn't kill him?
Is that what you're saying?
Am I wrong?
Well, who knows?
I always thought of her as kind of a small
-time crook who wouldn't
even watch a guy die,
let alone kill him.
But maybe she just snapped.
Wait, what'd you say?
She's not small-time!
Is she all you think of?
He's alive!
Well, he was.
I hope he still is.
Geez, Nami.
You sure know how to trash a place.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just resting a little, that's all.
You mean to tell me that
pouring over a treasure
map after wrecking a
house is how you relax?
You're not fooling me.
Now Vice up already.
What's bothering you?
It's okay.
You can tell me anything, remember?
Something happened to make me mad.
It's nothing.
Those guys. Who are they?
You know?
Yeah, I met some captain guy.
He seemed kind of liar-ish, though.
Now I see.
Yeah, that would hit her heart.
To think that someone
actually showed up for her.
Friends.
That word means pain.
It breaks her heart.
Usopp!
Did Nami do all this to you?
Sorry, Zoro and I did that. No, you did.
Luffy, you're here now.
Yep, sure am.
I'm here too. Hi there.
One of these days, I'll kill you.
Oh, you just made a
full recovery. Shut up!
Oh, and by the way, we kind of
heard you were dead, killed by Nami.
Stupid Johnny, he was spouting
nonsense that entire time.
Well, in a way, it is the truth.
But I'm alive, cause you see,
she actually saved my life.
Looks to me like she's got
some sort of hidden motive
for hanging out with a
bunch of renegade fishmen.
Obviously?
Fine, what next?
We're gonna destroy Arlong Park?
Whoa, hang on just a second,
don't you think we better find out
what's going on with Nami first?
It's no use either way Huh?
No matter what you guys do, Arlong's
rule won't come to an end. No, Gecko.
Who's she?
Nami's big sister. What?
Nami's sister?
No wonder she's so hot.
What do you mean that it's no use?
Just trust me.
Don't get yourselves involved
in what's going on here.
And leave poor Nami alone.
I'll explain the situation.
And if that doesn't get you to
leave, I don't know what will.
Look!
There's a marine ship at the shore!
It's Bridge 16th ship!
Maybe headquarters is finally taking
action after what happened to Branch 77.
I'm Colonel Nezumi of Branch 16.
Now then, Genzo, please step up
and make it snappy. Yes, Colonel.
I'm the one you're looking for.
You, huh?
Take me to Nami's house
at once. Nami? But why?
I don't understand
what's going on, Colonel.
Lead the way.
That is all you need to do.
As I watched the sunrise,
I began to wonder What could be
the reason it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you!
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me?
I'll do what I must be.
Cause they're everything I want will be!
Pack these arms around my dreams.
And pull us back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way.